http://www.envisn.com/privacy-copyright-liability

Privacy Statement
Envisn is committed to providing our visitors with a web site that respects their privacy. We do not gather personal information such as your name, phone number, or e-mail address unless you supply it voluntarily, for example, by contacting us via e-mail, fax, regular mail, or registering in a secure portion of the site. Any personal information you provide is protected under either Federal or State legislation relative to the protection and privacy of personal information. This means that, at the point of collection, you will be informed that your personal information is being collected, the purpose for which it is being collected, and that you have a right of access to the information. This web site contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the content and the privacy practices of other web sites and encourage you to examine each site's privacy policy and make your own decisions regarding the accuracy, reliability and correctness of material and information found.
Copyright Notice
In using this website and its contents, you agree that the content is provided by Envisn The content of this website is protected by copyrights, trademark and other proprietary rights. You acknowledge that these rights are valid, and that your use of the content of this website will be governed by applicable copyright, trademark and other intellectual property laws. The content of this website is protected by US and international copyright laws and Envisn owns a copyright for the content and the coordination, arrangement and any enhancement of such content. You may make copies of all or part of the content for your personal use, provided that you must ensure that any copyright, trademark or other proprietary rights notices associated therewith are included in such copy, exactly as they appear in the original content. Except as specifically provided herein, none of the content of this website shall be copied, modified, published, sold or transferred, in whole or in part, without the prior written consent of Envisn.
Limitation of Liability
Neither Envisn nor any of its affiliated corporations will be liable to any third party with respect to any of the content of this website, nor any use of or reliance on such content or materials by any third party. Furthermore, neither Envisn nor any of its affiliated corporations will be liable for any damages (including special or consequential damages) or injury caused by any failure of performance, error, omission, interpretation, defect, unauthorized access to or alteration of, this website. The foregoing limitation of liability is subject to applicable law.
Cognos Toolsfrom Envisn
NetVisnAutoVisnUniVisnDocuVisn
Cognos Resources
Envisn’s IBM Cognos BlogCustom Query LibraryTutorial VideosMastering Cognos SecurityContent Store Survival GuideExpert Guide to Cognos Audit Data
Contact Envisn
Request a DemoSupport978-779-0400info@envisn.com
Latest Cognos Posts
233 Ayer Road,  Harvard, MA 01451 USAServing North America, Europe, and the UK with plans to expand to other areas in the near future. Privacy, Copyright & Liability
